hey boss little juice huh good man where
are you headed Tampa I'm gonna go see my
lady Anita damn big guy your lady's a
real smoke joke tell me boss I wish you
could get on a video chat with me though
or a phone call for that matter
brother I'm in the same boat with my
girl afrodite
met her on a Facebook Messenger she's
actually gonna come visit me but then
she she got in a crazy uh jet ski
God blessed her in the upper torso
region if you catch my trip thanks boss
all natural
something funny uh no all right well
just so you know I'd rather suck horse
and let you disrespect my woman
experiencing a temporary drop in cabin
pressure oh I actually have angina
phobia which is a fear of low oxygen for
the uninformed I gotta get out of here
ha
hey big boys
[Music]
foreign